all right guys I have a pretty Epic Mod
here this is actually really epic so
what it does is it adds Birds to the
game so here I built a little bird cage
so let's go ahead on in shut the door so
they don't go out and you can look at
them this is the
peacock pretty cool isn't it this is the
Bluebird just a baby one
pean Flamingo I thought was pretty cool
that is pretty cool they they also make
noise when you kill them it's why my
sound on this video is a little bit
higher just so you can hear the noise
they make it's a runner it's it actually
runs pretty fast and then a white
peacock so it adds all these birds to
the game and these are the some of the
items they can drop and there's a bunch
of recipes and different items you can
make with this stuff but it adds five
new Birds Bunches of items and it's
really cool cuz the birds just spawn in
biomes and stuff and I don't know I
would really recommend you download this
mod just brighten up your Minecraft
worlds and stuff and when you're just
walking around and you just see random
Birds it's actually something I'm
surprised is a mod and isn't part of the
game it's really cool I like it and they
free roam and everything and they spawn
in certain biomes I thought it was
really really cool just download it and
you know you you'll come across these
birds it gives you new items to build
and new animals to look for and things
like that brightens up your world I
thought it was pretty cool and hopefully
you do and obviously I'm not going to
keep these birds in caged I'll set them
free not going to harm these birds I
don't know why I said that but anyways
thanks for watching um hope you do
download this mod it's in the
description just adds a couple Birds to
your World liens it up and makes
Minecraft more fun so thanks for
watching